All our similarities, they're building me up yeah
我们之间相似点，将我塑造
They're building me up yeah, they're building me up
将我塑造，将我塑造
It was all too much for me, I thought I'd give up but now I'm stronger
他曾经困扰着我，我曾想过放弃，但我现在更强大
You could be the remedy, it's heating me up yeah
你可做我的救赎，让我热血沸腾
It's heating me up yeah, it's heating me up
让我热血沸腾，让我热血沸腾
You are of a different breed, I'm bringing you up to speed
你是独特的物种，我带你了解一切
Enlighten me
启发了我
Shake off the dust and look around, you're above the clouds
拂去尘埃，环视四周，你在云端之上
If you've been wondering how realize that you're lucid now
如果你想知道 你是否还清醒
You've got to
你需要
Amplify, it's the spark from you and I that keeps this world alive
放大，烟火来自你和我，让这个世界鲜活
Amplify, you are the reason why our connection is by design
放大，你就是那理由，我们的相遇是必然
Amplify, it's the spark from you and I that keeps this world alive
放大，烟火来自你和我，让这个世界鲜活
Amplify, you are the reason why our connection is by design
放大，你就是那理由，我们的相遇是必然
It's not a coincidence, you're more than you know now
这并不是巧合，你的潜力无限
You're more than you show now, there's more than you know
只展现了一点，很多等你发现
It's not enough to take it in, you've got to use what's deep within
仅仅了解 还是不够，你要用心的去感受
Shake off the dust and look around, you're above the clouds
拂去尘埃，环视四周，你在云端之上
If you've been wondering how realize that you're lucid now
如果你一直想知道如何意识到你现在是清醒的
You've got to
你必须
Amplify, it's the spark from you and I that keeps this world alive
放大，烟火来自你和我，让这个世界鲜活
Amplify, you are the reason why our connection is by design
放大，你就是那理由，我们 相遇是必然
Amplify, it's the spark from you and I that keeps this world alive
放大，烟火来自 你 和我，让这世界鲜活
Amplify, you are the reason why our connection is by design
放大，你就是那理由，我们相遇是必然
It's just not enough, you see, to leave it to chance
那是远远不够，你看，就顺其自然
This is a rare circumstance
这是罕见的情况
Get up and make it your, make it your dance
起身让它被你掌控，让它成为你的舞台
You are in the centre now, I'm letting you know
你正在舞台中央，我会让你知道
It's time to set it aglow, it's time to get up and get up and go
是时候点燃舞台，是时候冲向未来
Amplify, it's the spark from you and I that keeps this world alive
放大，烟火来自 你 和我，让这个世界鲜活
Amplify, you are the reason why our connection is by design
放大，你就是那理由，我们 相遇是必然
Amplify, it's the spark from you and I that keeps this world alive
放大，烟火来自 你 和我，让这个世界鲜活
Amplify, you are the reason why our connection is by design
放大，你就是那理由，我们 相遇是必然
Our connection is by design
我们 相遇是必然